James E. McDonald papers, (1904-1997)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup I: UFO Research Files, 1904-1971
  - Series I: General Files, A-Z, 1945-1971
    - Hynek, J. Allen: Articles, reviews, correspondence, memos from MAFB / BB case file, Playboy article, sequels, JAH statements, clippings. (Box 6)
    - Hypnosis and Relata. (Box 6)
    - Identifications: Good examples. (Box 6)
    - International Get Acquainted Program: Europe: International UFO Bureau. (Box 6)
    - Interstellar Travel: Paul R. Hill (unpublished article). (Box 6)
    - Institute for Policy Studies. (Box 6)
    - Ithaca, NY: Mrs. Rita Malley. 12/12/67 (Box 6)
    - Jacksonville, Oregon: Vogel. (Box 6)
    - JANAP 146: AFR 200-2: AFR 80-17: Government silencing. (Box 6)
    - Jannereth, Kenneth D.: Houghton Lake, Michigan. 7/16/64 (Box 6)
    - Japan: Fukuoka. 11/15/48 (Box 6)
    - Japanese UFO materials (in Japanese). (Box 6)
    - Johnson, A. W.: Voice of America (VOA). (Box 6)
    - Johnson, Dave: Boise, Idaho. (Box 6)
    - Jones, Conway: Newton, Georgia. 11/22/68 (Box 6)
    - Joplin, Missouri: Photos. 1/13/67 (Box 6)
    - Journal, Personal: JEM: 1st: Early cases. 2/16/58-6/29/62 (Box 6)
    - Journal, Personal: JEM: 2nd, (35 pp.). 4/66-6/24/67 (Box 6)
    - Journal, Personal: JEM: 3rd (Australian trip). 6/21-7/8/67 (Box 6)
    - Journal, Personal: JEM: 4th, (49 pp.). 4/28/68-3/17/71 (Box 6)
    - Junita, PA. 8/27/56 (Box 6)
    - Kaliszewski, J. J. 10/11/51 (Box 6)
    - Kalnicki, Mrs. Jean: Dorchester, Mass: Photos. 4/23/66 (Box 6)
    - Kassander, A. Richard: Institute of Atmospheric Physics. (Box 6)
    - Keel, John Kenney, David A.: Encampment, WY. 7/6/47 (Box 6)
    - Kerstetter, Forrest J.: West Cameron, PA. 2/19/67 (Box 6)
    - Keyhoe, Major Donald E. (Box 6)
    - Kibel, James J. (Box 6)
    - Killian Case. 2/24/59 (Box 6)
    - Kincheloe AFB: Kansas City, KS. 9/11-12/61 (Box 6)
    - Kincheloe AFB: Klass critique King, Mrs. A. M.: Nairobi, Kenya. (Box 6)
    - King, John T.: Bangor, Maine. 3/23/66 (Box 6)
    - Kinlock, Elizabeth Lake Victoria Spring. 1954 (Box 6)
    - Klass, Philip J.: NICAP Report, ONR Controversy (2 folders). (Box 7)
    - Korean Cases. (Box 7)
    - Kratovil, Capt. C. J. 6/1/54 (Box 7)
    - Krebs, James A.: Paxinos, PA. 1/18/67 (Box 7)
    - Kuiper, Gerard P.: University of Arizona Lunar & Planetary Lab. (Box 7)
    - Kuntz, Dr. Albert B.: Houston, TX. 1/21/67 (Box 7)
    - Lakenheath-Benyesyrtd Sightings. 8/12-13/56 (Box 7)
    - La Madera, NM: Hynek's lack of investigation. 4/26/64 (Box 7)
    - Lapp, Ralph. (Box 7)
    - Larson, June: Researcher, Washington State. (Box 7)
    - Laub Engineering. (Box 7)
    - Lazer: Physiological Damage: Space Research. (Box 7)
    - Leary, Thomas P.: Omaha, Nebraska. (Box 7)
    - Leawood, Kansas: Nicholl, Tom H. 7/3/67. (Box 7)
    - Leick, Mr. H.. 11/22/66 (Box 7)
    - Legenhausen, Lee: Blair, Nebraska: Photo: Frank Edwards. 1967 (Box 7)
    - Levelland, TX Cases: Photo (map): Slide negatives. (Box 7)
    - Library of Congress: "Facts about UFOs". 5/5/66 (Box 7)
    - Life International: Whipple, A. B. C. (Box 7)
    - Lightfoot, David: Amarillo TX. 4/8/50 (Box 7)
    - Light Paralysis: Light Flash Response. (Box 7)
    - Little Rock, Arkansas: Captains Anderson and Adams. 3/18/50 (Box 7)
    - Loburak, Carol Ann: Lansdale, PA. 11/58 (Box 7)
    - Loch Raven Dam. 11/26/58 (Box 7)
    - London Observer: (CIA, Robertson Report involvement). (Box 7)
    - Longview, Washington: Cdr. M. B. Taylor. 7/3/49 (Box 7)
    - Lore-Denault. (Box 7)
    - Lore, Gordon I. R. Jr.: NICAP. (Box 7)
    - Los Alamos Scientific Laboratory Lubbock. (Box 7)
    - Lights: W. L. Ducker. (Box 7)
    - Lundahl, Arthur C.: Bethesda, MD. (Box 7)
    - McClelland, Clark: Cape Kennedy NICAP. (Box 7)
    - McDonald, Edward N.: LeRoy, Ohio. (Box 7)
    - McDonald, James E.: Address Lists. (Box 7)
    - McDonald, James E.: Bibliography: Valerie Vaughan. (Box 7)
    - McDonald, James E.: Correspondence after JEM's death. (Box 7)
    - McDonald, James E.: Corres. and itineraries. 10/1-12/31/69 (Box 7)
    - McDonald, James E.: Corres. and itineraries. 1/1-3/31/70 (Box 7)
    - McDonald, James E,: Corres. and itineraries. 8/1-12/31/70 (Box 7)
    - McDonald, James E.: Corres. and itineraries. 4/1-7/31/70 (Box 7)
    - McDonald, James E.: Corres. and Itineraries. 9/67-9/70 (Box 7)
    - McDonald, James E.: Hypothesis: Extraterrial. (Box 7)
    - McDonald, James E.: Notes. (Box 7)
    - McDonald, James E.: Press. 1966-70 (Box 7)
    - McDonald, James E.: Press: WNEW-TV Panel on the Hill case. (Box 7)
    - McDonald, James E.: Talk: Arizona Academy. 1/8/68 (Box 7)
    - McDonald, James E.: Talk: IEEE Santa Monica, CA. 6/9/70 (Box 7)
    - McDonald, James E.: Las Vegas, NV. 2/70 (Box 7)
    - McDonald, James E.: Talk: Space Science Lecture: NC. 2/70 (Box 7)
    - McDonald, James E.: Talks. 1966-67 (Box 7)
    - McDonald, James E.: Talks. 1968-69 (Box 7)
    - McDonald, James E.: Talks Summary List. 11/5/66-5/28/69 (Box 7)
    - McDonald, James E.: Trip. 10/23/67 (Box 7)
    - McDonald, James E.: Trip, Westinghouse TV Series. (Box 7)
    - McDonald, James E.: UFO publications. (Box 8)
    - Magerko, Parma OH. 11/16/56 (Box 8)
    - Magor, John: Editor, Canadian UFO Report. (Box 8)
    - Magnetic UFO Detectors. (Box 8)
    - Malone, Thomas F. (Box 8)
    - Maney, Prof. Charles A. (Box 8)
    - Manhattan Beach, CA. 7/27/52 (Box 8)
    - Mantell, Captain: Classic case. (Box 8)
    - Marrow: Flemington, NJ. (Box 8)
    - Martin, Mrs. John S. 3/6/57 (Box 8)
    - Mass Displacement Cases: dv/dt. (Box 8)
    - Maxwell AFB I. (Box 8)
    - Maxwell AFB II. (Box 8)
    - Maxwell AFB Case Lists. (Box 8)
    - Meagher, Silvia: Index to. The UFO Evidence. (Box 8)
    - Menzel, Donald. (Box 8)
    - Menzel, Donald: Haneda, Japan "explanation." (Box 8)
    - Merced, CA.: Lt. Akins,. ca. 1956 (Box 8)
    - Meteorologists' Observations. (Box 8)
    - Meteors re. UFO Problems. (Box 8)
    - Methuen, MA. 1/20/67 (Box 8)
    - Michalak, Steve: Winnipeg. 5/20/67 (Box 8)
    - Michel, Aime: French researcher: Correspondence. (Box 8)
    - Middle East: Israel, etc. (Box 8)
    - Midwest: Oklahoma, etc. August 1965 (Box 8)
    - Miley's Eleven (11) Radar Cases: Henry A. Miley. (Box 8)
    - Milford, Ohio. 2/11/67 (Box 8)
    - Milledgeville, Georgia. 11/20/67 (Box 8)
    - Miller, Gene: Banning, CA. 11/14/55 (Box 8)
    - Minot AFB, North Dakota. 8/24/66 (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Articles, etc. (Box 8)
    - Molder, Prof. Sannu: McGill University. (Box 8)
    - Monon: RR case. (Box 8)
    - Montrose, Colorado. 5/21/50 (Box 8)
    - Moore, Charlie B.: Balloon research, other cases, input, Zamora. (Box 8)
    - Moos, Stan. 8/4/68 (Box 8)
    - Morges, William S.: Massachusetts case. (Box 8)
    - Muroc AFB. 7/8/47 (Box 8)
    - Murphy, William M.: Redding, CA. 6/10/67 (Box 8)
    - Muza, Mark: Poquuson, VA. 11/19/59 (Box 8)
    - National Amateur Astronomers (NAA). Aug 20-23, 1969 (Box 8)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA): Astronaut sightings. (Box 8)
    - NASA. 1966-1968 (Box 8)
    - NASA: JEM proposal. 1/16/68 (Box 8)
    - List of JEM papers, talks. (Box 8)
    - Nash, Leigh: Tucson, AZ. 5/8/68 (Box 8)
    - Nash, William B., Fortenberry, William. 7/14/52 (Box 8)
    - National Academy of Sciences. (Box 8)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Council. (Box 8)
    - National Enquirer: Article, JEM letter to Donahue. 2/17/67 (Box 8)
    - National Science Foundation. 1967 (Box 8)
    - National Science Foundation: Proposal Notes. 1970 (Box 8)
    - Naval Ordnance Laboratory. 1968 (Box 8)
    - Naval Ordnance Station. 1967 (Box 8)
    - Navy: Cases and Relata (Second file). (Box 8)
    - Nazi "Flying Saucers." (Box 8)
    - Nebo, NC: Mrs. E. H. Thomason. 3/15/57 (Box 8)
    - Nemuro, Hokkaido. 2/7/53 (Box 8)
    - Nenana, Alaska. 1/22/52 (Box 8)
    - New Guinea Cases. (Box 8)
    - New Haven, West Virginia. 4/17/67 (Box 8)
    - Newman Forum: Albuquerque. (Box 8)
    - Newsletters: CRIFO: Len Stringfield. (Box 9)
    - Newsletters: FSIC Bulletin: Flying Saucers Invest. (Box 9)
    - Newsletters: Kansas Newsletter, The. (Box 9)
    - Newsletters, miscellaneous. (Box 9)
    - Newton, N.H. July 27, 1967-Sept. 8, 1967. (Box 9)
    - New York TIMES: JEM. 1966-67 (Box 9)
    - New Zealand: Correspondence, etc. (Box 9)
    - New Zealand: Fulton, Harold: Angel hair. (Box 9)
    - New Zealand: Moreland, Mrs. Frederick. July 13, 1959 (Box 9)
    - Niagara Falls. 7/25/57 (Box 9)
    - National Investigations Committee on Aerial Phenomena (NICAP) Breakup. 1969/70 (Box 9)
    - NICAP: Correspondence: Hall, Lore, Nixon, etc. (Box 9)
    - NICAP: Leonard Wolf, Congressman: Statement. (Box 9)
    - NICAP Massachusetts Committee: Fowler, Ray: Misc. reports. (Box 9)
    - NICAP Massachusetts Investigating Committee Report. (Box 9)
    - NICAP Reports: Miscellaneous (3 folders.) (Box 9)
    - NICAP: UFO Investigator. 1966-67 (Box 9)
    - NICAP: UFO Investigator. 1968-70 (Box 9)
    - NICAP: UFO Reports. 1967 (Box 9)
    - JEM interviews. 1947 (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous Clips, General Notes and Letters. 1950 (Box 9)
    - Nogales Notes. (Box 9)
    - Norris, Peter E. (Box 9)
    - North Atlantic Case: William D. Bridge, San Diego. 2/8/51 (Box 9)
    - North Island, San Diego, CA: Broka. 12/50 (Box 9)
    - Novel, Gordon. 11/1/69 (Box 9)
    - OAS Aerospace education: Seattle. 8/68 (Box 9)
    - Occupants. 1964-65 (Box 9)
    - Occupants Relata. '66-'68 (Box 9)
    - Ochsner, Dr. Warren B. Homer, NY. April 11, 1964 (Box 9)
    - Oceanic Lake Transits Frank Draki, Carl Sagan, B. A. Nison. (Box 9)
    - Odessa, Wash. 12/10/52 (Box 9)
    - Olsen, Tom M UFO Information Retrieval Center. (Box 9)
    - Office of Naval Research (ONR) (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Contract No. 2173. (3 folders) (Box 9)
    - ONR Funds Controversy: Klass, JEM White Papers. (Box 9)
    - ONR Funds Controversy: JEM notes, miscellaneous materials. (Box 9)
    - ONR Hughes, Jim. (Box 9)
    - ONR Laufer, A. R.: Redlands, etc. (Box 10)
    - ONR London. (Box 10)
    - undated (Box 10)
    - Oracle Junction, AZ. July 2, 1968 (Box 10)
    - Outage: Articles, correspondence. 11/9/65 (Box 10)
    - Outage: Publications, etc. 11/9/65 (Box 10)
    - Outages:. 1966-1968 (Box 10)
    - Outages: Northeast. 1965 (Box 10)
    - Outages: Power. 11/9/65 (Box 10)
    - Overstreet, William: Elmer, Missouri. 3/4/69 (Box 10)
    - Oxnard, CA. March 23, 1957 (Box 10)
    - Pacific Ocean. 7/11/59 (Box 10)
    - Padrick, Sid. (Box 10)
    - Sid Page, Thornton: AAAS Symp: Article Encyclopedia Britannica. (Box 10)
    - Page, Tony: Texas. (Box 10)
    - Panel, Scientists to Study UFOs: Proposal, NAS / Coleman. 1966 (Box 10)
    - Paranormal Research: Dowsing, Vietnam. (Box 10)
    - Parapsychology. (Box 10)
    - Paris, TX. 3/7/67 (Box 10)
    - Parham, B. E.: Lavonia, Georgia. 6/29/64 (Box 10)
    - Patuxent R. Naval Air Station. 12/19/64 (Box 10)
    - People Problems. (Box 10)
    - Perna Photos: Frank Edwards: Lake Tiorati. Blair, Nebraska. (Box 10)
    - Pestalozzi, Rudy: B-36 case. (Box 10)
    - Petit, Ronald. (Box 10)
    - Petty, Paul T. 7/24/48 (Box 10)
    - Pfeiffer, R. James: Life Magazine shot. (Box 10)
    - P-51 Cases: Gorman; Vandalia; Mantell; Bellefontaine; Lake Mead. (Box 10)
    - Philip, Mrs. John R.: Canberra. (Box 10)
    - Photo Notes: James Lucci Photo and others. (Box 10)
    - Physics Colloquim: JEM. 10/5/66 (Box 10)
    - Physiological. (Box 10)
    - Piri Reis Maps. (Box 10)
    - Piute County, Utah: Ray S. Whittaker. 8/49 (Box 10)
    - Port Huron, Michigan. 7/29/52 (Box 10)
    - Portage County, Ohio: Pittsburgh NICAP Subcommittee. 4/17/66 (Box 10)
    - Portage County Ohio: Ravenna, Dale Spaur. (Box 10)
    - Powell, William C.: Radnor, PA. 5/21/66 (Box 10)
    - Project "Blue Book": Miscellaneous cases and Air Force correspondence. 1953 (Box 10)
    - Project "Grudge". 1951 (Box 10)
    - Project Grudge Sightings: JEM List. (Box 10)
    - Project "Sign". 1949 (Box 10)
    - Project "Stork". 1952 (Box 10)
    - Project "Twinkle". 1951 (Box 10)
    - Propulsion: See also Space Travel. (Box 10)
    - Pseudo science. (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Psychological Effects: Don Piccard. (Box 10)
    - Psychological Effects: Miscellaneous. (Box 10)
    - Psychological and Hallucinations. (Box 10)
    - Quotes, JEM List of. (Box 11)
    - Radar. (Box 11)
    - Radar observations: Miscellaneous. (Box 11)
    - Rand Corporation. 1967-68 (Box 11)
    - Rapid City, South Dakota. (Box 11)
    - Rawlins, Mrs. E. G. 4/28/47 (Box 11)
    - Rayburn, E. L.: Twin Falls, Idaho. 9/7/56 (Box 11)
    - RB-47 Case: Blue Book. (Box 11)
    - RB-47-Lakenheath cases: Original Radar-visuals. (Box 11)
    - Red Bluff, CA. 8/13/60 (Box 11)
    - Redlands, CA. 2/4/68 (Box 11)
    - Redmond, OR. 9/25/59 (Box 11)
    - References, UFO Materials: JEM list. (Box 11)
    - Reporting Possibilities. (Box 11)
    - Rhodes, William A.: Photos. 7/7/47 (Box 11)
    - Richied, Carol A.: Woodland, CA. 2/13/67 (Box 11)
    - Richmond, Indiana: 5/24/54: (See Saunders / Harkins p. 69). (Box 11)
    - Richmond, VA. 6/24/66 (Box 11)
    - Richmond, VA: USWB: Minoczewski. 4/47 (Box 11)
    - Ridicule Lid. (Box 11)
    - Ring-clouds: Life Magazine. (Box 11)
    - Robertson Report. 1953 (Box 11)
    - Romney, Mrs. Gordon M: Sydney, Australia. 1904 (Box 11)
    - Rose, Francis Leopold: Australia: sighting. ca. 1900 (Box 11)
    - Roush, J. Edward Congressman. 1967-68 (Box 11)
    - Rubicam, Bettina: Phoenix. 1969 (Box 11)
    - Ryan Case: AAL. 4/8/56 (Box 11)
    - Sagan, Carl. (Box 11)
    - San Carlos Lake, AZ. 11/6/68 (Box 11)
    - Sanderson, Ivan T. (Box 11)
    - Sandia Corporation: Box 5800, Albuquerque, NM 97775. (Box 11)
    - Sandoval, Julian: Albuquerque, NM. 6/23/66 (Box 11)
    - Satellites, Natural. (Box 11)
    - Satellite Objects. (Box 11)
    - Saunders, David: Corres., Orthoteny theory, Pre-pub. Drafts of UFOs? Yes! (Box 11)
    - Scandinavian UFO Correspondence. (Box 11)
    - Scenic, South Dakota: Robert E. Driscoll. 5/27/67 (Box 11)
    - Schirmer, Herb: Ashland, Nebraska. 12/3/67 (Box 11)
    - Schwartz, Dr. Berthold E. (Box 11)
    - Scientists and Engineers. (Box 11)
    - Scully, Frank: "Behind the Flying Saucers". 1947-50 (Box 11)
    - Scully, Orville: Casper, WY: Summer. 1966 (Box 11)
    - Seattle, WA: Moriarty, Mrs. E. J.. 8/12/67 (Box 11)
    - Seay, Henry: Fayetteville, Arkansas. 7/4/47 (Box 11)
    - Sebago, The, Coast Guard cutter. 11/5/57 (Box 11)
    - Secret Technology Hypothesis. (Box 11)
    - Shallett, Sidney: Articles. April 30 / May 7, 1949 (Box 11)
    - Shaw, Allan: Hobart, Southern Tasmania: Slides. (Box 11)
    - Shrum and Cerny: Miscellaneous. (Box 11)
    - Skyballs: Fortean. (Box 11)
    - Skyhooks and Research Balloons. (Box 11)
    - Small-arms Fire. (Box 11)
    - Smith, E. J.. 7/4/47 (Box 11)
    - Smithsonian Center for Short-lived Phenomena. (Box 11)
    - Snippy Case: Alamosa, Colorado. 10/67 (Box 11)
    - Socorro, NM Landing: Fused sand invest; Moore, Charles B.; Zamora, Lonnie. 4/24/64 (Box 11)
    - Sonic Booms & Explosions. (Box 11)
    - Soukup, Joseph J.: Cleveland, Ohio. 11/58 (Box 11)
    - Southbridge, MA. 9/13/67 (Box 11)
    - Space Animal Hypothesis. (Box 11)
    - Space Flight. (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Space Science Committee (NASA): Grant request:, rejected. 1968 (Box 11)
    - Space Science Grant: Expenditures Report. (Box 11)
    - Sperry, Capt. Willis T.: AA case. 5/29/50 (Box 11)
    - Spooner, Wisconsin. 4/8/53 (Box 11)
    - Spraggett, Allen: Canadian Broadcasting Corp. (Box 11)
    - Spruill, C. L.: North San Juan, CA.: 6/1/67 (Box 11)
    - Squyres, William V.: Pittsburgh, Kansas. 8/25/52 (Box 11)
    - Supersonic Transport (SST): JEM Congressional Testimony. (Box 11)
    - Staley, D. O.: Correspondence. (Box 12)
    - Stadvec, Ernest: Akron, Ohio. 7/4-5/61 (Box 12)
    - Steinmetz, Ken: National Amateurs Astronomers, Denver. (Box 12)
    - Stevenson, G. Bruce: Mansfield, Ohio. 2/1/48 (Box 12)
    - Stranges, Frank E. (Box 12)
    - Strauch, Art A.: St. George MN. 10/2/65 (Box 12)
    - Stratospheric Clouds: "ring-cloud." (Box 12)
    - Stringfield, Len: Correspondence. (Box 12)
    - Sub-sun Case. (Box 12)
    - Sullivan, Mrs. William. (Box 12)
    - Susanville, CA: Edward A. Grant. 9/14/63 (Box 12)
    - Swamp Gas. (Box 12)
    - Symposium Clippings. 7/29/68 (Box 12)
    - Tape Transcriptions: JEM: Witnesses, etc: Summaries, JEM. (Box 12)
    - Taylor, George E.: Ottsville, PA. 9/6/67 (Box 12)
    - Taylor, Senator Sam T.: Mt. Mestas, Colorado. 11/25/55 (Box 12)
    - Temple City Sightings: Druffel, LANS, NICAP. May 1966 (Box 12)
    - Tenoper, Don: Beatrice, Neb. 4 August 1965 (Box 12)
    - Testimony and Recall. (Box 12)
    - Theology and Philosophy. (Box 12)
    - Thibault, Frank T.: (Frank T. Thibault Collection). (Box 12)
    - Thomas, Steve: Omaha. 11/2/68 (Box 12)
    - Thompson, William H.: Municipal University of Omaha. (Box 12)
    - Tillamook, Oregon. 3/13-14/67 (Box 12)
    - Time travel hypothesis. (Box 12)
    - Tirman, Col. Robert M.: Southeast Asia. 3/14/69 (Box 12)
    - Tombaugh, Dr. Clyde: (Astronomer Sighting). 8/20/54 (Box 12)
    - Totten, Bertram A.: L.O.C.: DCA. 3/26/50 (Box 12)
    - Tremonton, Utah, D.C. Newhouse. 7/2/52 (Box 12)
    - Trinidad, Colorado. 3/23/66 (Box 12)
    - Trindad Isle Photos: Overall, Zan Corres. 1/16/58 (Box 12)
    - Trittipoe, Theresa: AA encounter: El Paso, NM. 1/16/67 (Box 12)
    - Tucson Area Sighting. 4/1/58 (Box 12)
    - Tucson Luminous Objects. 11/7/65 (Box 12)
    - Tully Nests. (Box 12)
    - Tunguska Explosion, Siberia (Also Mars' moons): Seers, Stan. (Box 12)
    - Twin Falls, Idaho: Photos. 8/13/47 (Box 12)
    - Twinkle, Project. (Box 12)
    - Udall, Morris K., Congressman. (Box 12)
    - Udvardy, Jeno: Vicksburg, Michigan. 3/31/67 (Box 12)
    - Uehling, Dr. Edwin: "Dr. X": University of Washington. (Box 12)
    - Unidentified Flying Objects (UFO): Articles: General. (Box 12)
    - UFO: Articles: Life, Look, Newsweek, Saturday Review. (2 folders) (Box 12)
    - UFO: Articles: Space & Extraterrestrial Life. (Box 12)
    - UFO: Articles: Time. (Box 12)
    - UFO: Articles, True Magazine. (Box 12)
    - UFO: Articles, U.S. News and World Report. (Box 12)
    - UFO: Bibliographies: Martin Sabel and Doubt. (Box 12)
    - UFO Cases: List by JEM: Evaluations. (Box 12)
    - UFO Clips: Australian. 1954-1967 (Box 12)
    - UFO Clips: Chronological. 1950-1954 (Box 12)
    - UFO Clips: Chronological. 1955-58 (Box 13)
    - UFO Clips: Chronological. 1959-64 (Box 13)
    - UFO Clips: Chronological. 1965- June 1966 (Box 13)
    - UFO Clips: Chronological. 9/66-12/66 (Box 13)
    - UFO Clips. January 1967 (Box 13)
    - UFO Clips: February. 1967 (Box 13)
    - UFO Clips: March. 1967 (Box 13)
    - UFO Clips. April 1967 (Box 13)
    - UFO Clips. May 1967 (Box 13)
    - UFO Clips. June 1967 (Box 13)
    - UFO Clips. July 1967 (Box 13)
    - UFO Clips. August 1967 (Box 13)
    - UFO Clips. September 1967 (Box 13)
    - UFO Clips. October 1967 (Box 13)
    - UFO Clips. November - December 1967 (Box 13)
    - UFO Clips. January - March 1968 (Box 13)
    - UFO Clips: Miscellaneous. (Box 13)
    - UFO Education Courses. (Box 13)
    - UFO Investigation Center (UFOIC): Australia (Photos). (Box 13)
    - UFOIC Newsletter: Australian. (Box 13)
    - UFO Journals: Anomaly, Ed. John A. Kee. (Box 14)
    - UFO Journals: Apro Bulletin. May 1958 thru Nov-Dec 1965 (Box 14)
    - UFO Journals: Apro Bulletin. Nov-Dec '66 thru May-June '71 (Box 14)
    - UFO Journals: Australian Flying Saucer Review. (Box 14)
    - UFO Journals: Canadian UFO Report. (Box 14)
    - UFO Journals: Saucer News, Editor-in-chief, Gray Barker. (Box 14)
    - UFO Journals: Scientific: Icarus. (Box 14)
    - UFO Journals: Scientific: Science.: William Markowitz controversy. (Box 14)
    - UFO Reports. January-June 1968 (Box 14)
    - UFO Reports. July-September 1968 (Box 14)
    - UFO Reports. October-December 1968 (Box 14)
    - UFO Reports. 1969 (Box 14)
    - UFO Reports: Clippings & Duplicates. (Box 14)
    - UFO Reports: Miscellaneous. (Box 14)
    - UFOs: Pre-1800: Hawaii; Japan; Seneca; Cicero; India vimanas. (Box 14)
    - UFO Sightings: Miscellaneous. (Box 14)
    - Uman, Martin: Westinghouse, re. Klass. (Box 14)
    - Union, Robert B.: Deer Lodge, Montana. 2/13/68 (Box 14)
    - United Aircraft Corporation & Travelers' Research Corporation. 1968 (Box 14)
    - United Nations. (Box 14)
    - University of California at Riverside: Series on Space Navigation and Space Beliefs. (Box 14)
    - University Research Society of America: File #300. (Box 14)
    - University of Washington: Hazard Lockard sightings. (Box 14)
    - U.S. Air Force: List of Unidentifieds. 1952-1967 (Box 14)
    - USS Delarof Case. 7/45 (Box 14)
    - USSR: A. A. Tikhanov; Y. A. Fomin; Fedor Y. Zigel; General Porfiri Stolyarov; Anatoly Stolyarov. (Box 14)
    - USSR: Translated by Irving Ames from "Technology and Youth." (Box 14)
    - USSR: Zigel Pleas: UFO Study, Russian. (Box 14)
    - U Thant Utica, New York: Capt. Robert W. Fox. 6/23/55 (Box 14)
    - Uzunoglu, Dr. V.. 8/1/66 (Box 14)
    - Vallee, Jacques. (Box 14)
    - Van Cleef, Mrs. Shirley C.: Tucson, AZ. 6/61 (Box 14)
    - Vandalia, Ohio. 3/8/50 (Box 14)
    - Van Winkle PAA: near San Juan, Puerto Rico. 3/9/57 (Box 14)
    - Vashon Island. (Box 14)
    - Venavle, David, Attorney: Washington, D.C. (Box 14)
    - Volunteer Flight Officers Network (VFON). 1966-67 (Box 14)
    - VFON: 1966-67: Herb E. Roth, Director VFON. 1969-71 (Box 14)
    - Vietnam. 5/5/67 (Box 14)
    - Vintner, Captain Lawrence: Sioux City, Iowa. 1/20/51 (Box 14)
    - Walter, Clara: Tucson. 4/8/66 (Box 14)
    - Walton, Dr. and Mrs. George: Rodeo, NM. 9/25/67 (Box 14)
    - Wanaque Reservoir, NJ. 1/66 (Box 14)
    - Washington National Airport. 7/52 (Box 14)
    - Warren, Ohio. 7/8/68 (Box 14)
    - Watson, Mrs. Lola: Nickel sample: Photos. (Box 14)
    - Weather Balloons. (Box 14)
    - Weather Data: U.S. Air Force. 10/6/67 (Box 14)
    - Webb, Walter N.: Hayden Planetarium, Boston. (Box 14)
    - Weber, Cdr. Robert W.: Miramar. 1951 (Box 14)
    - Weitzel, William B. White Sands. 3/2/67 (Box 14)
    - White Sands 3/2/67 (Box 15)
    - White Sands 3/2/67 (Box 15)
    - Whitmore, Dr. Robert A.: San Jose, CA. 4/25/52 (Box 15)
    - Whittier, CA: "Mexican Hat Dance" UFOs. 8/22/57 (Box 15)
    - Wiegner, A. A. 9/23/54 (Box 15)
    - Wildcat article: JEM. 5/21/68 (Box 15)
    - Wilson, Paul W.: Yucca Valley, CA. 3/21/69 (Box 15)
    - Winkel, Joseph J.: Springfield, IL. 7/20/64 (Box 15)
    - Wistor, Joe W.: Sandia, NOTS. 1947-48 (Box 15)
    - Wood, Dr. Robert M.: McDonnell-Douglas. (Box 15)
    - Woodruff, Dr. R. S.: Vermont. 1/4/65 (Box 15)
    - Wright Brothers, etc. (Box 15)
    - Wright, Col. Howard T.: B-25 Texas case. 1/16/57 (Box 15)
    - Yankee Atomic Plant: Haddam, Connecticut. 9/13/67 (Box 15)
    - Yarger, Doug. 9/17/69 (Box 15)
    - Yorba Linda Photos. 1/24/67 (Box 15)
    - Yuma, AZ. 4/52, 2/4/53; 7/18/69 (Box 15)
  - Series 2: Project Blue Book, 1947-1968
    - June 1947: Hamburg, NY. (Box 15)
    - June 2, 1947: Rehobuth Bomen, Delaware. (Box 15)
    - June 12, 1947: Weiser, Idaho. (Box 15)
    - June 14, 1947: Bakersfield, California. (Box 15)
    - June 21, 1947: Spokane, Washington. (Box 15)
    - June 24, 1947: Portland, Oregon. (Box 15)
    - June 24, 1947: Idaho. (Box 15)
    - June 28, 1947: Montgomery, Alabama. (Box 15)
    - June 28, 1947: Rockfield, Wisconsin. (Box 15)
    - June 28, 1947: 30 miles NW Lake Mead, Nevada. (Box 15)
    - June 29, 1947: Las Cruces, New Mexico. (Box 15)
    - June 30, 1947: Williams AFB, Arizona. (Box 15)
    - July 3, 1947: S. Brooksville, ME. (Box 15)